Bonowitz, Abraham J.; Papers apap186
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- General Correspondence, 1993-2014; 3; 1.2 cubic ft.
  - A. Bonowitz to Senators Bateman and Lesniak, 2011 March 10 (Box 1 (3-General Correspondence), Folder 187)
  - Phyllis Hatfield, 2011 March 12 (Box 1 (3-General Correspondence), Folder 188)
  - NCADP Maryland Action Alert, 2011 April 4 (Box 1 (3-General Correspondence), Folder 189)
  - Julie M. Mazzei (Kent State), 2011 April 22 (Box 1 (3-General Correspondence), Folder 190)
  - NCADP Notice about Setback in Connecticut, 2011 May 11 (Box 1 (3-General Correspondence), Folder 191)
  - A. Bonowitz to NCADP Staff, 2011 August 3 (Box 1 (3-General Correspondence), Folder 192)
  - Barbara Weinstein, 2011 August 24 (Box 2 (3-General Correspondence), Folder 1)
  - EJUSA Mailing, 2011 December 1 (Box 2 (3-General Correspondence), Folder 2)
  - A. Bonowitz to A. Colette Rice, 2012 January 19 (Box 2 (3-General Correspondence), Folder 3)
  - Prof. Ari Kohen, 2012 March 30 (Box 2 (3-General Correspondence), Folder 4)
  - Jeanne Woodford, 2012 July 2 (Box 2 (3-General Correspondence), Folder 5)
  - Email Regarding Phone Meeting Agenda, 2012 July 5 (Box 2 (3-General Correspondence), Folder 6)
  - ACLU Membership Mailing, 2013 January 10 (Box 2 (3-General Correspondence), Folder 7)
  - Victor Ramirez (Maryland), 2013 January 24 (Box 2 (3-General Correspondence), Folder 8)
  - Michael G. Summers to Beth Wood, 2013 January 28 (Box 2 (3-General Correspondence), Folder 9)
  - Gov. Martin O'Malley (MD) to Chairman Brian Frosh, 2013 February 21 (Box 2 (3-General Correspondence), Folder 10)
  - Deleware Police Chief's Council to Deleware General Assembly, 2013 March 12 (Box 2 (3-General Correspondence), Folder 11)
  - A. Bonowitz to Catholics Mobilizing Network, 2013 November 4 (Box 2 (3-General Correspondence), Folder 12)
  - A. Bonowitz Email Correspondence and Notes, 2013 (Box 2 (3-General Correspondence), Folder 13)
  - Thank-You Letters from Various Organizations, 2013-2014 (Box 2 (3-General Correspondence), Folder 14)
  - A. Bonowitz to Diann Rust-Tierney, 2014 January 28 (Box 2 (3-General Correspondence), Folder 15)
  - A. Bonowitz to AIUSA Re: Application for Position, 2014 June 26 (Box 2 (3-General Correspondence), Folder 16)
  - A. Bonowitz to Gov. Haley Barbour, Undated (Box 2 (3-General Correspondence), Folder 17)
  - NCADP Email Update, Undated (Box 2 (3-General Correspondence), Folder 18)
  - Mailings of Representative's Contact Info to NCADP Members, Undated (Box 2 (3-General Correspondence), Folder 19)
  - Bishop McNamara High School Thank-You Note, Undated (Box 2 (3-General Correspondence), Folder 20)
  - Note Left on Bonowitz Vehicle Explaining Biblical Precedent for the Death Penalty, Undated (Box 2 (3-General Correspondence), Folder 21)
- General Memorabilia, 1984-2015; 4; 14.1 cubic ft.
  The General Memorabilia series comprises of activist buttons, T-shirts, and an array of different objects collected by Abe Bonowitz associated to his work to end the death penalty.
  - 10th Annual Fast & Vigil to Abolish the Death penalty, Abolition Action Committee, June29-July 2, Undated (Oversized 18, Item 1)
  - 16th Annual Fast & Vigil to Abolish the Death Penalty ,Abolition Action Committee, 2009 June 29-July 2 (Oversized 21, Item 2)
  - 17th Annual Fast & Vigil to Abolish the Death Penalty by Abolition Action Committee, 2010 June 29-July 2 (Oversized 21, Item 5)
  - 18th Annual Fast & Vigil to Abolish the Death Penalty, Abolition Action Committee, 2011 (Oversized 17, Item 5)
  - 19th Annual Fast & Vigil to Abolish th Death Penalty, Abolition Action Committee, 2012 June 29-July 2 (Oversized 18, Item 3)
  - 1st Annual Death Penalty Abolitionist Leadership Training Institution, Washington D.C, National Coalition To Abolish the Death Penalty, 2008 August 6-8 (Oversized 13, Item 5)
  - 2nd Annual Death Penalty Abolitionist Leadership Training Institute, National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty, 2009 August 1-3 (Oversized 19, Item 3)
  - 2nd Annual Death Penalty Abolitionist Leadership Training, the National Coalition To Abolish the Death Penalty, 2009 August 1-3 (Oversized 22, Item 9)
  - 30 Years Later, The Death Penalty is Still: Stop Executions Now!, Abolitionist Action Committee, 2006 (Oversized 21, Item 7)
  - 35 Years Later, The Death Penalty is Still: Stop Executions Now!, Abolitionist Action Committee, Undated (Oversized 23, Item 2)
  - 3rd Annual Death Penalty Abolitionist Leadership Training for the National Coalition To Abolish the Death Penalty, 2010 August 14-15 (Oversized 21, Item 6)
  - 4th Annual Fast & Vigil to Abolish the Death Penalty, Abolition Action Committee, June 29-July 2, Undated (Oversized 18, Item 2)
  - 8th Annual Fast & Vigil to Abolish the Death Penalty by Abolition Action Committee, June 29-July 2, Undated (Oversized 18, Item 8)
  - A World Gone Queer Tshirt, 1991 (Oversized 10, Item 3)
  - Abolish the Death Penalty, Undated (Oversized 22, Item 4)
  - Abolish the Death Penalty for the National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty, Undated (Oversized 23, Item 1)
  - Abolition: Starvin for Justice '05 by Abolitionist Action Committee, 2005 (Oversized 23, Item 3)
  - Abolition: Starvin for Justice '05 by Abolitionist Action Committee, 2005 (Oversized 23, Item 4)
  - Accessory- "Free Texas of the Death Penalty", Undated (Oversized 29, Item 1)
  - Accessory- "Fry Eggs Not People: People of Faith Against the Death Penalty", Undated (Oversized 29, Item 2)
  - Accessory- Removeable tattoos, Undated (Oversized 29, Item 3)
  - American Justice?: Every Year in the United States 4 Innocent People Are Sentenced to Death, the National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty, Undated (Oversized 22, Item 8)
  - Amnesty International 30 years Working For Human Rights, 1991 (Oversized 10, Item 6)
  - Amnesty International black, Undated (Oversized 21, Item 9)
  - Amnesty International pink, Undated (Oversized 21, Item 8)
  - Amnesty International, Midwestern Student '93 University Tshirt, 1993 (Oversized 10, Item 5)
  - Amnesty International: Annual General Meeting Los Angeles, California, 1992 (Oversized 11, Item 2)
  - Amnesty International: These Monsters are Real, Undated (Oversized 11, Item 1)
  - An Eye for An Eye Makes The World Blind, Undated (Oversized 14, Item 6)
  - Bad Boy Bail Bonds Exercise Your 8th Amendment Right, C. Jeffrey Stanley, Undated (Oversized 12, Item 5)
  - Badges- Congressional Black Caucus, Undated (Oversized 33, Item 3)
  - Badges- DE Repeal Project, Undated (Oversized 33, Item 6)
  - Badges- Equal Justice USA, Undated (Oversized 33, Item 15)
  - Badges- MARO Regional Confernece, Undated (Oversized 33, Item 10)
  - Badges- National Coalition to Abolish Death Penalty, Undated (Oversized 33, Item 1)
  - Badges- Reform Jewish Advocates for Justice, Undated (Oversized 33, Item 4)
  - Badges- Salsa Community Conference 2011, Undated (Oversized 33, Item 11)
  - Badges- Southern Ohio Correctional Facility, Undated (Oversized 33, Item 2)
  - Badges- Spin Academy, Undated (Oversized 33, Item 7)
  - Badges- TCADP Anuual Conference, Undated (Oversized 33, Item 5)
  - Badges- Training for the Long Run, Undated (Oversized 33, Item 12)
  - Badges-Governmental Affairs Agent, Undated (Oversized 33, Item 13)
  - Badges-Humanisn on the Rise, Undated (Oversized 33, Item 9)
  - Badges-Journey of Hope, Undated (Oversized 33, Item 8)
  - Badges-Maryland Death Penalty Abolish Campaign, Undated (Oversized 33, Item 14)
  - Bag- "Abe: National Coalition to Abolish Death Penalty", Undated (Oversized 27, Item 9)
  - Bag- "Journey of Hope", Undated (Oversized 27, Item 8)
  - Bag- "National Coalition to Abolish Death Penalty", Undated (Oversized 27, Item 7)
  - Bag- "National Coalition to Abolish Death Penalty: Affiliate Member", Undated (Oversized 27, Item 2)
  - Bag- "National Coalition to Abolish Death Penalty: Affiliate Member", Undated (Oversized 27, Item 5)
  - Bag- "Stop Executions: Texas Coalition to Abolish Death Penalty", Undated (Oversized 27, Item 3)
  - Bag- "Texas Coalition to Abolish Death Penalty", Undated (Oversized 27, Item 1)
  - Bag- "Training for the Long Run: NCADP Louisville, Kentucky", Undated (Oversized 27, Item 6)
  - Bag- "Training for the Long Run: NCADP", Undated (Oversized 27, Item 4)
  - Bexley Class of 84, 1984 (Oversized 12, Item 7)
  - Bracelet- " Not on our Watch: Save Darfur", Undated (Oversized 28, Item 4)
  - Bracelet- "Execute Justice, Not people!", Undated (Oversized 28, Item 1)
  - Bracelet- "Execute Justice, Not people!", Undated (Oversized 28, Item 2)
  - Bracelet- "See bully, Stop a bully", Undated (Oversized 28, Item 3)
  - Bracelet-" There is no such thing as a lesser person", Undated (Oversized 28, Item 5)
  - Bull Horn- "National Day of Action to Close Guantanamo", Undated (Oversized 25, Item 4)
  - Bull Horn- "National Day of Action to Close Guantanamo", Undated (Oversized 25, Item 5)
  - Bush T-shit, Undated (Oversized 19, Item 4)
  - California Innocence Project, Undated (Oversized 11, Item 3)
  - ConnecticutNetwork to Abolish the death penalty, Execute Justice not People, Undated (Oversized 17, Item 2)
  - Death By State Who's The Murderer Now?, Undated (Oversized 18, Item 7)
  - Do The MathYour Rights+My Rights Human Rights, the National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty, Undated (Oversized 22, Item 5)
  - Don't Kill For Me! Floridians For Alternatives To The Death Penalty, Undated (Oversized 22, Item 1)
  - ELLA Foundation: Empathy. Love.Lessons. Action, Undated (Oversized 17, Item 4)
  - END The Death penalty World Wide!, Undated (Oversized 15, Item 3)
  - Every Vote, Every Voter Counts in 2004, International Election Monitors (Oversized 12, Item 8)
  - Execute Art Not People, Undated (Oversized 14, Item 4)
  - Execute Justice Not People, Death Penalty Focus, Undated (Oversized 14, Item 2)
  - Execution is NOT the Solution, Alaskans Against the Death Penalty, Undated (Oversized 20, Item 4)
  - From Violence To Healing Journery of Hope,Virginians Against the Death Penalty, Undated (Oversized 17, Item 9)
  - Fry Fish Not People, Nebraskans Against the Death Penalty, Alaskans Against the Death Penalty, Undated (Oversized 20, Item 5)
  - Fry Okra,Not People ,People of Faith Against the Death Penalty, Undated (Oversized 17, Item 3)
  - Glad to be Sad: Melankolic, Undated (Oversized 12, Item 1)
  - Got Proof?, Death Penalty Focus, Undated (Oversized 14, Item 3)
  - Green Peace T-shirt, Undated (Oversized 10, Item 1)
  - Greetings from the Struggle, National Organizers Alliance, Undated (Oversized 13, Item 4)
  - Hat- "Human Rights Have No Borders", Undated (Oversized 25, Item 1)
  - Hat- "National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty", Undated (Oversized 25, Item 1)
  - Have a Nice Day!, Undated (Oversized 11, Item 4)
  - Honor: A Benefit For The Honor The Earth Campaign, Undated (Oversized 10, Item 2)
  - How can our Killing People who Kill People teach Children that Killing is Wrong?, Undated (Oversized 17, Item 10)
  - Human Rights and the Environment Make the Connection, EarthRights International, Undated (Oversized 19, Item 5)
  - Human Rights Now!, Reebok Foundation, 1988 (Oversized 11, Item 5)
  - Human Rights Workers' Rights The Same Struggle, Undated (Oversized 12, Item 6)
  - I am Troy Davis, Amnesty International, Undated (Oversized 16, Item 1)
  - I Oppose The Death Penalty Children's black shirt, Undated (Oversized 12, Item 2)
  - I Oppose The Death Penalty Children's blue shirt, Undated (Oversized 12, Item 3)
  - I Oppose The Death Penalty Children's pink vest, Undated (Oversized 12, Item 4)
  - I Oppose The Death Penalty Don't Kill For Me, Abolitionist Action Committee, Undated (Oversized 21, Item 3)
  - ICADP Death Penalty Hope T-shirt, Illinios Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty, Undated (Oversized 18, Item 6)
  - Journey of Hope End the Cycle of Violence, 2003 (Oversized 15, Item 4)
  - Journey of Hopefrom Violence to Healing, Undated (Oversized 19, Item 2)
  - Love is a Basic Human Right, Amnesty International, Undated (Oversized 13, Item 3)
  - Magnets: Miscellaneous, Undated (Oversized 30, Item 1)
  - Making Strides toward Aboliton and Reconciliation: Pilgrimage of Rememberance Raleigh, NC to Washington D.C, 2008 June (Oversized 21, Item 1)
  - Memorbilia Plate, Undated (Oversized 25, Item 3)
  - Mercy: Musicians Encouraging Repeal of Capital Punishment, 2005 October 6 (Oversized 18, Item 4)
  - Montana Abolition Coalition Ending the Death Penalty, Undated (Oversized 18, Item 5)
  - Murder Victims Families For Reconciliation, Undated (Oversized 17, Item 7)
  - Murder Victims' Families for Reconciliation: Death Penalty= False Promise for Victims, Undated (Oversized 21, Item 4)
  - National Coalition to Abolish The Death Penalty Shirt, Undated (Oversized 19, Item 1)
  - NCACP 2004: Annual Conference Washington D.C (Oversized 13, Item 1)
  - NCADP derechos humans! Abolish the Death Penalty, the National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty, Undated (Oversized 22, Item 6)
  - Nebraskans Against the Death Penalty, Undated (Oversized 20, Item 3)
  - No Death Penalty No More Executions, Undated (Oversized 15, Item 2)
  - Orange & Osceola Public Defender Ninth Judicial Circuit, Undated (Oversized 13, Item 2)
  - Pins- Miscellaneous, Undated (Oversized 34, Item 1)
  - Pins- Miscellaneous, Undated (Oversized 34, Item 1)
  - Pins- Miscellaneous, Undated (Oversized 35, Item 1)
  - Pro-Life, Undated (Oversized 14, Item 8)
  - Replace the Death Penalty Justice That Works, Undated (Oversized 17, Item 8)
  - Replace the Death Penalty Yes on 34 Justice That Works, Undated (Oversized 24, Item 3)
  - Save Life: CatholicAgainstTheDeathPenalty, Undated (Oversized 16, Item 2)
  - Shaka Man, Undated (Oversized 11, Item 7)
  - Sign- Miscellaneous, Undated (Oversized 32, Item 5)
  - Sign- National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty, Undated (Oversized 32, Item 3)
  - Sign- Netroots Nation, Undated (Oversized 32, Item 2)
  - Sign- Thou Shall Not Kill, Undated (Oversized 32, Item 4)
  - Sign- United Farm Workers of America, Undated (Oversized 32, Item 1)
  - Starvin' for Justice '15 22nd Annual Fast & Vigil to Abolish the Death Penalty, 2015 (Oversized 24, Item 1)
  - Sticker- American Civil Liberties Union, Undated (Oversized 31, Item 1)
  - Sticker- Amnesty International, Undated (Oversized 31, Item 3)
  - Sticker- Amnesty International Support/Member 2015, Undated (Oversized 31, Item 13)
  - Sticker- Journey of Hope, Undated (Oversized 31, Item 7)
  - Sticker- Law Enforcement Against Prohibition, Undated (Oversized 31, Item 8)
  - Sticker- Maryland Citizens Against State Executions, Undated (Oversized 31, Item 10)
  - Sticker- Miscellaneous, Undated (Oversized 31, Item 15)
  - Sticker- Moratorium Campaign, Undated (Oversized 31, Item 14)
  - Sticker- Music for America, Undated (Oversized 31, Item 12)
  - Sticker- National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty, Undated (Oversized 31, Item 9)
  - Sticker- NJADP, Undated (Oversized 31, Item 5)
  - Sticker- PADP, Undated (Oversized 31, Item 4)
  - Sticker- Progressives United, Undated (Oversized 31, Item 6)
  - Sticker- TCASK, Undated (Oversized 31, Item 2)
  - Sticker- Texas Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty, Undated (Oversized 31, Item 11)
  - Stop Executions! Texas Coalition to Abolish The Death Penalty, Undated (Oversized 22, Item 3)
  - Stop Executions Now- Walk to Stop Executions Death House to the Capital, 2015 October 4-10 (Oversized 24, Item 2)
  - Stop Executions Now! Sweatshirt, Undated (Oversized 16, Item 3)
  - Stop Executions Now!, Abolition. Org, Undated (Oversized 15, Item 1)
  - Stop State Killings, Undated (Oversized 20, Item 6)
  - Tennesseans for Alternatives to the Death Penalty- Honoring Life by Abolishing the Death Penalty, Undated (Oversized 24, Item 4)
  - TEXAS: No More Killing, Undated (Oversized 23, Item 6)
  - The Death Penalty A Flawed System 111 Reasons Why, The Moratorium Campaign, Undated (Oversized 14, Item 1)
  - The New Mexico Coalition To Repeal The Death Penalty, Undated (Oversized 22, Item 2)
  - The Secret of the Policeman's Toe Jam: Drumzard Wires, Box of Nails, Sour Grapes, Men of Leisure, Amnesty International, Undated (Oversized 11, Item 6)
  - Travel Mug- "Abolish the Death Penalty", Undated (Oversized 26, Item 4)
  - Travel Mug- "Equal Justice USA", Undated (Oversized 26, Item 2)
  - Travel Mug- "Making a Difference Everyday", Undated (Oversized 26, Item 1)
  - Travel Mug- "Rachel's Fund: Abolish the Death Penalty", Undated (Oversized 26, Item 6)
  - Travel Mug- "Starvin' For Justice: Abolish the Death Penalty", Undated (Oversized 26, Item 3)
  - Travel Mug- "Starvin' For Justice: Abolish the Death Penalty", Undated (Oversized 26, Item 5)
  - Travel Mug- "Starvin' For Justice: Abolish the Death Penalty", Undated (Oversized 26, Item 8)
  - Travel Mug- "Stop Executions: texas Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty", Undated (Oversized 26, Item 9)
  - Travel Mug- "Training for the Long Run: NCADP", Undated (Oversized 26, Item 7)
  - Under Our Wings: A Global Approach to End Juvenile Injustice Las Vegas, Nevada 2nd Annual National Conference, 2013 December 8-10 (Oversized 17, Item 1)
  - Virginians for Alternatives to the Death Penalty, Undated (Oversized 20, Item 2)
  - Voices Against the Death Penalty: Witness to Innocence From Death Row to Freedom, Undated (Oversized 13, Item 6)
  - Voices Against the Death Penalty: Witness to Innocence From Death Row to Freedom, Undated (Oversized 20, Item 1)
  - Vote or Die, Undated (Oversized 10, Item 8)
  - We Watch the World, Amnesty International Tshirt, Undated (Oversized 10, Item 4)
  - Who Would Jesus Execute? Abolish the Death Penalty Now!, Undated (Oversized 14, Item 5)
  - Why Do We Kill People Who Kill People to Show that Killing People is Wrong?, Undated (Oversized 14, Item 7)
  - You Have The Right to Not Remain Silent: Race Still Matters, Undated (Oversized 23, Item 5)
- Statewide Abolition Groups, 1994-2015; 5; 2.2 cubic ft.
  The Statewide Abolition Groups are all of the different groups from states fighting to end the death penalty in their respective state.
  - Alaskans Against the Death Penalty, 2003-2009; Undated (Box 1 (5-Statewide Abolition Groups), Folder 1)
  - Arkansas Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty, 2009-2010; Undated (Box 1 (5-Statewide Abolition Groups), Folder 2)
  - California- Death Penalty Focus of California, 1994-1999; 2015 June; Undated (Box 1 (5-Statewide Abolition Groups), Folder 3)
  - Coloradans Against the Death Penalty, 2009; Undated (Box 1 (5-Statewide Abolition Groups), Folder 4)
  - Connecticut Network to Abolish the Death Penalty, 2013; 2015; Undated (Box 1 (5-Statewide Abolition Groups), Folder 5)
  - Delaware Citizens Opposed to the Death Penalty (1 of 3), 2008-2010; 2013-2016; Undated (Box 1 (5-Statewide Abolition Groups), Folder 6)
  - Delaware Citizens Opposed to the Death Penalty (2 of 3), 2008-2010; 2013-2016; Undated (Box 1 (5-Statewide Abolition Groups), Folder 7)
  - Delaware Citizens Opposed to the Death Penalty (3 of 3), 2008-2010; 2013-2016; Undated (Box 1 (5-Statewide Abolition Groups), Folder 8)
  - Floridians for Alternatives to the Death Penalty (1 of 2), 1998-2010; Undated (Box 1 (5-Statewide Abolition Groups), Folder 9)
  - Floridians for Alternatives to the Death Penalty (2 of 2), 1998-2010; Undated (Box 1 (5-Statewide Abolition Groups), Folder 10)
  - Georgians for Alternatives to the Death Penalty, 1996-2015; Undated (Box 1 (5-Statewide Abolition Groups), Folder 11)
  - Illinois Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty, 2010-2011; Undated (Box 1 (5-Statewide Abolition Groups), Folder 12)
  - Indiana Information Center or the Abolition of Capital Punishment, 2004-2005; Undated (Box 1 (5-Statewide Abolition Groups), Folder 13)
  - Kansas Coalition Against the Death Penalty, 2008-2012; Undated (Box 1 (5-Statewide Abolition Groups), Folder 14)
  - Kentucky Coalition Against the Death Penalty, 2015; Undated (Box 1 (5-Statewide Abolition Groups), Folder 15)
  - Louisiana Coalition for Alternatives to the Death Penalty, 2011 (Box 1 (5-Statewide Abolition Groups), Folder 16)
  - Maryland Citizens Against State Executions ( 1 of 2), 2004-2013; Undated (Box 1 (5-Statewide Abolition Groups), Folder 17)
  - Maryland Citizens Against State Executions ( 2 of 2), 2004-2013; Undated (Box 1 (5-Statewide Abolition Groups), Folder 18)
  - Maryland Citizens Against State Executions- Materials on Senate Bill 279, 2008 (Box 2 (5-Statewide Abolition Groups), Folder 1)
  - Maryland Citizens Against State Executions Materials on Senate Bill 276 + House Bill 295, 2013 (Box 2 (5-Statewide Abolition Groups), Folder 2)
  - Missourians for Alternatives to the Death Penalty, 2004-2009 (Box 2 (5-Statewide Abolition Groups), Folder 3)
  - Montana Abolition Coalition- Ending the Death Penalty, Undated (Box 2 (5-Statewide Abolition Groups), Folder 4)
  - Nebraskans Against the Death Penalty, 2001; 2008; 2015; 2016 March 31 (Box 2 (5-Statewide Abolition Groups), Folder 5)
  - New Mexico Coalition to Repeal the Death Penalty, 2009-2014; Undated (Box 2 (5-Statewide Abolition Groups), Folder 6)
  - New Yorkers Against the Death Penalty, 2004-2007; Undated (Box 2 (5-Statewide Abolition Groups), Folder 7)
  - Ohioans to Stops Executions ( 1 of 3), 1996-2014; Undated (Box 2 (5-Statewide Abolition Groups), Folder 8)
  - Ohioans to Stops Executions ( 2 of 3), 1996-2014; Undated (Box 2 (5-Statewide Abolition Groups), Folder 9)
  - Ohioans to Stop Executions (3 of 3), 1996-2014; Undated (Box 2 (5-Statewide Abolition Groups), Folder 10)
  - Ohioans to Stops Executions Tribute, 2013 September- October (Box 2 (5-Statewide Abolition Groups), Folder 11)
  - Oklahoma Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty, 2010; Undated (Box 2 (5-Statewide Abolition Groups), Folder 12)
  - Oregon Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty, 1996-2005; Undated (Box 2 (5-Statewide Abolition Groups), Folder 13)
  - Pennsylvania For Alternatives to the Death Penalty, 2004-2010; Undated (Box 2 (5-Statewide Abolition Groups), Folder 14)
  - South Carolinians Abolishing the Death Penalty, 2009; Undated (Box 2 (5-Statewide Abolition Groups), Folder 15)
  - Tennesseans for Alternatives to the Death Penalty, 2004-2010; Undated (Box 2 (5-Statewide Abolition Groups), Folder 16)
  - Texas Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty ( 1 of 2), 2004-2015; Undated (Box 2 (5-Statewide Abolition Groups), Folder 17)
  - Texas Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty ( 2 of 2), 2004-2015; Undated (Box 2 (5-Statewide Abolition Groups), Folder 18)
  - Utahns For Alternatives to the Death Penalty, 2010; Undated (Box 2 (5-Statewide Abolition Groups), Folder 19)
  - Virginians for Alternatives to the Death Penalty ( 1 of 2), 2003-2011; 2015 May; Undated (Box 3 (5-Statewide Abolition Groups), Folder 1)
  - Virginians for Alternatives to the Death Penalty ( 2 of 2), 2003-2011; 2015 May; Undated (Box 3 (5-Statewide Abolition Groups), Folder 2)
  - Washington Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty, 2010 October (Box 3 (5-Statewide Abolition Groups), Folder 3)
  - Wisconsin Interfaith Impact- The Death Penalty, 2004; Undated (Box 3 (5-Statewide Abolition Groups), Folder 4)
- National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (NCADP), 1987-2015; 6; 2.8 cubic ft.
  This series contains board of directors materials, conference materials, newsletters, and reports about the death penalty. The National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (NCADP) is a national organization devoted to abolishing the death penalty. Numerous materials in this series are regarding the Abolitionist Leadership Training Institute (ALTI). This series is restricted. It is arranged alphabetically.
  - Abolution Rising Awards Dinner Program, ca. 2006 (Box 1 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 1)
  - Abolution Rising Draft On-Site Staff Plan, 2008 January (Box 1 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 2)